{
  "Entertaiment": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Who is the most followed person on instagram?",
      "Answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option1": "Airana Grande",
      "option2": "Kylie Jenner",
      "option3": "Lionel Messi",
      "option4": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which of the following indian has won the oscar? ",
      "Answer": "Satyajit Ray",
      "option1": "Priyadarshan",
      "option2": "Yash Chopra",
      "option3": "Anurag Kashyap",
      "option4": "Satyajit Ray",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which is the highest grossing movie in india?",
      "Answer": "Avengers:Endgame",
      "option1": "Avengers:Infinity War",
      "option2": "The Jungle Book",
      "option3": "FF8",
      "option4": "Avengers:Endgame",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which of the following indian actor has shared sliver screen with tom cruise?",
      "Answer": "Anil Kapoor",
      "option1": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option2": "Anupam Kher",
      "option3": "Irrfan Khan",
      "option4": "Anil Kapoor",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which of the following movie was released in theaters?",
      "Answer": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
      "option1": "Gulabo Sitabo",
      "option2": "Laxmi bomb",
      "option3": "Ludo",
      "option4": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Aishwarya Rai was crowned Miss World in which year?",
      "Answer": "1994",
      "option1": "1995",
      "option2": "1993",
      "option3": "1996",
      "option4": "1994",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Who is known as the 'father of Indian Cinema'",
      "Answer": "Dadasaheb Phalke",
      "option1": "Dadasaheb Torne",
      "option2": "Satyajit Ray",
      "option3": "V. Shantaram",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Lata Mangeshkar awarded with Bharat Ratna in the year",
      "Answer": "2001",
      "option1": "1998",
      "option2": "2003",
      "option3": "2005",
      "option4": "2001",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Real name of Rajnikant?",
      "Answer": "Shivaji Rao Gaekwad",
      "option1": "Shivaji Rao Deshmukh",
      "option2": "Shivaji Rao ",
      "option3": "Shivaji ",
      "option4": "Shivaji Rao Gaekwad",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Who is the first indian movie star to be featured on the cover of Time magazine",
      "Answer": "parveen Babi",
      "option1": "Zeenat Aman",
      "option2": "Amir Khan",
      "option3": "Aishwarya Rai",
      "option4": "parveen Babi",
      "weight": 1
    }
  ],
  "com": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Ctrl, Shift and Alt are called .......... keys.",
      "Answer": "modifier",
      "option1": "modifier",
      "option2": "function",
      "option3": "adjustment",
      "option4": "alphanumeric",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "MS-Word is an example of _____",
      "option1": "An operating system",
      "option2": "A processing device",
      "option3": "Application software",
      "Answer": "Application software",
      "option4": "An input device",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "A computer cannot 'boot' if it does not have the _____",
      "option1": "Compiler",
      "option2": "Loader",
      "option3": "Operating System",
      "Answer": "Operating System",
      "option4": "Assembler",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "By default, your documents print in ________ mode",
      "option1": "Landscape",
      "option2": "Portrait",
      "Answer": "Portrait",
      "option3": "Page Setup",
      "option4": "Print View",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which of the following is a popular programming language for developing multimedia webpages",
      "option1": "COBOL",
      "Answer": "Java",
      "option2": "Java",
      "option3": "Basic",
      "option4": "Assembler",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The first computer was programmed using .......",
      "option1": "Assembly language",
      "Answer": "Machine Language",
      "option2": "Machine Language",
      "option3": "Spaghetti code",
      "option4": "Source code",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The computer's processor consists of the following parts",
      "option1": "CPU and Main memory",
      "option2": "Hard Disk and Floppy Drive",
      "Answer": "Control Unit and ALU",
      "option3": "Control Unit and ALU",
      "option4": "OS and Application",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "A _______ is a software program used to view Web pages.",
      "option1": "site",
      "option2": "host",
      "option3": "link",
      "Answer": "browser",
      "option4": "browser",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Where is RAM located?",
      "Answer": "Mother Board",
      "option1": "Mother Board",
      "option2": "Expansion Board",
      "option3": "External Drive",
      "option4": "None",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which key is used in combination with another key to perform a specific task?",
      "option1": "Function",
      "option2": "Spacebar",
      "option3": "Arrow",
      "option4": "Control",
      "Answer": "Control",
      "weight": 1
    }
  ],
  "lit": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Who among the following writers won the 2017 Sahitya Academy Award for Hindi literature?",
      "option1": "Niranjan Mishra",
      "option2": "Ramesh Kuntal Megh",
      "Answer": "Ramesh Kuntal Megh",
      "option3": "Uday Narayana Singh",
      "option4": "Shrikant Deshmukh",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Name the first Indian to get Nobel prize in literature.",
      "option1": "Amartya Sen",
      "option2": "Lal Bahadur Shastri",
      "option3": "CV Raman",
      "option4": "Rabindranath Tagore",
      "Answer": "Rabindranath Tagore",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which of the following awards is given in the field of literature?",
      "option1": "Arjuna Award",
      "option2": "Ashok Chakra",
      "Answer": "Vyas Samman",
      "option3": "Vyas Samman",
      "option4": "Bharat Award",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "The religious literature of the Jain at the early stage was written in",
      "option1": "Ardhamagadhi",
      "Answer": "Ardhamagadhi",
      "option2": "Pali",
      "option3": "Sanskrit",
      "option4": "None",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Who among the following has not received a Nobel Prize in literature",
      "option1": "Derek Walcott",
      "option2": "Pablo Neruda",
      "Answer": "Churchill",
      "option3": "Churchill",
      "option4": "Ernest Hemingway",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which poet is considered a national hero in Greece?",
      "option1": "John Keats",
      "option2": "Lord Byron",
      "Answer": "Lord Byron",
      "option3": "Solan",
      "option4": "Sappho",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Rupert Brooke wrote his poetry during which conflict?",
      "option1": "Boer War",
      "option2": "Second World War",
      "option3": "Korean War",
      "option4": "First World War",
      "Answer": "First World War",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "A pattern of accented and unaccented syllables in lines of poetry",
      "option1": "rhyme scheme",
      "Answer": "meter",
      "option2": "meter",
      "option3": "rhythm",
      "option4": "rhyme",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Applying human qualities to non-human things",
      "Answer": "personification",
      "option1": "personification",
      "option2": "onomatopoeia",
      "option3": "alliteration",
      "option4": "metaphor",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "A poem that tells a story with plot, setting, and characters",
      "option1": "lyric",
      "option2": "free verse",
      "Answer": "narrative",
      "option3": "narrative",
      "option4": "node",
      "weight": 1
    }
  ],
  "sport": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Rovers Cup is related to which of the following sports?",
      "Answer": "Football",
      "option1": "Football",
      "option2": "Cricket",
      "option3": "Hockey",
      "option4": "Tennis",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Who is the President of International World Games Association?",
      "Answer": "Jose Perurena Lopez",
      "option1": "Jose Perurena Lopez",
      "option2": "Andrew Parsons",
      "option3": "Duane Kale",
      "option4": "Robert Steadward",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "How many teams had participated in the 2018 Women’s Hockey World Cup?",
      "option1": "8",
      "option2": "16",
      "Answer": "16",
      "option3": "22",
      "option4": "20",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which Indian cricketer has scored the maximum runs in ODIs?",
      "option1": "Kapil Dev",
      "option2": "Sunil Gavaskar",
      "Answer": "Sachin Tendulkar",
      "option3": "Sachin Tendulkar",
      "option4": "Virat Kohli",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which is first Indian cricket tournament ?",
      "option1": "Bombey Series",
      "option2": "Pepsi Cup",
      "Answer": "Bombay Triangular",
      "option3": "Bombay Triangular",
      "option4": "None",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which of the following is first cricket club in India ?",
      "Answer": "Oriental Cricket Club",
      "option1": "Oriental Cricket Club",
      "option2": "Maharashtra Cricket Club",
      "option3": "East Indian Cricket Club",
      "option4": "Bombay Cricket Club",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Indian played their First T20 Match against _______.",
      "Answer": "South Africa",
      "option1": "South Africa",
      "option2": "Australia",
      "option3": "England",
      "option4": "Pakistan",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Total no. of players playing on the pitch in a hockey match is?",
      "Answer": "22",
      "option1": "22",
      "option2": "16",
      "option3": "20",
      "option4": "18",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "The dimensions of a Hockey field are?",
      "Answer": "91.4m X 55m",
      "option1": "91.4m X 55m",
      "option2": "92m X 55m",
      "option3": "92.5m X 56m",
      "option4": "91.4m X 56m",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Name the nation that won 2014 Kabaddi World Cup Men's title.",
      "Answer": "India",
      "option1": "India",
      "option2": "Bangladesh",
      "option3": "Japan",
      "option4": "Pakistan",
      "weight": 1
    }
  ],
  "gk": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "In which place in India can we find cave temples of three faiths?",
      "option1": "Agra",
      "Answer": "Ellora",
      "option2": "Ellora",
      "option3": "Delhi",
      "option4": "Madhurai",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which foreign influence is seen in the rock cut architecture of India?",
      "option1": "Indo-European",
      "option2": "Greek",
      "option3": "Arabic",
      "option4": "Persian",
      "Answer": "Persian",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which of these cities has the maximum number of historical monuments?",
      "option1": "Mumbai",
      "Answer": "Delhi",
      "option2": "Delhi",
      "option3": "Kolkata",
      "option4": "Punjab",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which monument was built in memory of a British monarch?",
      "option1": "King Richard Memorial",
      "option2": "Prince of Wales Memorial",
      "option3": "King George Memorial",
      "option4": "Victoria Memorial",
      "Answer": "Victoria Memorial",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Everyone knows 'The Taj Mahal'. It was built by the Emperor Shah Jahan, but for whom?",
      "option1": "Farida Mahal",
      "option2": "Mumtaz Mahal",
      "Answer": "Mumtaz Mahal",
      "option3": "Jahani Mahal",
      "option4": "Toba Begum",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which city in India has built a 15.8 m high 'Gandhi Stupa' dedicated to Mahatma Gandhi?",
      "option1": "Allahbad, UP",
      "option2": "Varodara, Gujarat",
      "option3": "Ranchi, Jharkhand",
      "option4": "Vijaywada, AP",
      "Answer": "Vijaywada, AP",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The architecture of the city of Cochin in Kerala reflects the influence of...?",
      "option1": "The Dutch",
      "option2": "The Portuguese",
      "option3": "The British",
      "option4": "All of these",
      "Answer": "All of these",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Where is the world's largest panoramic sculptural relief located?",
      "option1": "Pondicherry",
      "option2": "Kanchipuram",
      "option3": "Mahabalipuram",
      "option4": "Madhurai",
      "Answer": "Mahabalipuram",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "In which Indian city would you find the mosque with 'Shaking Minarets'?",
      "option1": "Allahbad",
      "option2": "Hyderabad",
      "option3": "Lucknow",
      "option4": "Ahmedabad",
      "Answer": "Ahmedabad",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which state is known as India's Spice Garden...?",
      "option1": "Bihar",
      "option2": "Kerela",
      "Answer": "Kerela",
      "option3": "Uttaranchal",
      "option4": "Karnataka",
      "weight": 1
    }
  ],

  "users": [
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "email": "jdfkihdf",
      "password": "4444",
      "result": "1",
      "id": "id"
    }
  ],
  "subject_data": [
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "subject_name": "lit",
      "highest_score": "23",
      "no_of_times_attempted": "3",
      "total_ques": 12,
      "max_marks": 12,
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "new": [{}]
}
